<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Covid-19</string>
    <string name="default_notification_channel_id">default</string>
    <string name="text_confirmed_cases">Confirmed Cases : %s</string>
    <string name="text_last_updated">Last Updated : %s</string>
    <string name="default_notification_channel_name">Covid-19 India</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    //////////////////////prevention cards/////////
    //mask
    <string name="mask_card_title">"Wear Mask"</string>
    <string name="mask_card_description">"Wear a mask in public places.\nAvoid touching face,nose and mouth."</string>
    //hand wash
    <string name="handwash_card_title">"Wash Hands"</string>
    <string name="handwash_card_description">"Clean your hands often.\nUse soap and water, or an alcohol-based hand sanitizer."</string>
    //social distancing
    <string name="socialdistancing_card_title">"Social Distancing"</string>
    <string name="socialdistancing_card_description">"Maintain at least 1 metre (3 feet) distance between yourself and others."</string>
    //cover while sneezing
    <string name="coverwhilesneezing_card_title">"Cover while sneezing"</string>
    <string name="coverwhilesneezing_card_description">"Cover your nose and mouth with your bent elbow or a tissue when you cough or sneeze."</string>
    //Stay at home
    <string name="stayhome_card_title">"Stay at home"</string>
    <string name="stayhome_card_description">"Stay at home.\nAvoid going to crowded places.\nSelf-isolate yourself even with minor symptoms."</string>
    ///////////////////////////////////////////
    //////////About covid 19///////////
    <string name="what_is_covid">"Coronavirus disease (COVID-19) is an infectious disease caused by a newly discovered coronavirus.\nMost people infected with the COVID-19 virus will experience mild to moderate respiratory illness and recover without requiring special treatment. Older people, and those with underlying medical problems like cardiovascular disease, diabetes, chronic respiratory disease, and cancer are more likely to develop serious illness."</string>
    <string name="how_to_protect_yourself_from_covid19">"The best way to prevent and slow down transmission is be well informed about the COVID-19 virus, the disease it causes and how it spreads. Protect yourself and others from infection by washing your hands or using an alcohol based rub frequently and not touching your face."</string>
    <string name="cause_of_spread">"The COVID-19 virus spreads primarily through droplets of saliva or discharge from the nose when an infected person coughs or sneezes, so it’s important that you also practice respiratory etiquette (for example, by coughing into a flexed elbow)."</string>
    <string name="treatment_for_covid">"At this time, there are no specific vaccines or treatments for COVID-19. However, there are many ongoing clinical trials evaluating potential treatments. WHO will continue to provide updated information as soon as clinical findings become available.""</string>


</resources>

